What are you looking at?
I… The Ye family?
I'm Ye Mingyu from the escort agency,
not the Ye family's Mingyu!
Uncle Mingyu.
No one is stopping you
from going back to the escort agency.
Let go first, all right?
I won't let go!
I'm not leaving her.
Go home.
Let go.
Go back.
- Go home.
- Don't touch me!
I'm sorry.
I've failed you.
I didn't protect you.
I didn't protect you!
Zhenzhen.
I miss you so much.
Can you come back and see me just once?
I think of you every day and every night.
I beg you.
Come see me…
See me just once.
Zhenzhen.
Lu Ji.
You…
He's my third uncle.
He has gone home.
Good job.
It has been a great day!
You're…
the cannon.
You're drunk.
Who says I'm drunk?
I'm not drunk.
I can't get drunk!
I can't get drunk.
I'm not drunk!
You're almost smashed.
Xiao Heng.
Li.
You're so handsome.
How shameless.
Do you know you're good-looking?
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
Xiao Heng, you're not a man.
You can't even get drunk!
Have you ever told the truth?
What about you,
Li?
After all that drinking,
you didn't tell the truth either.
Thank you, Duke Su.
Stand still.
I'll take you home.
Home?
I no longer have a home.
I advise you not to meddle with it.
Otherwise,
your family will fall apart
sooner or later.
What a coincidence.
I don't have a home either.
Where did Jiang Li go?
It's late.
You don't know either?
After her ladyship went to Mr. Ye Mingyu,
she asked me to come back myself.
She didn't say where she was going.
How frustrating.
There's a storm raging
in the middle of the night
with lightning and thunder.
Why aren't you worried?
Are you really her maid?
What's the use of worrying?
Worrying really works.
YE RESIDENCE
- Hurry.
- My lady.
She's drunk.
Why did you let her drink so much?
Who gave you the right?
- Who are you?
- I'm her benefactor.
Benefactor?
Master.
How are things
at the base?
Everything is fine.
Is everything also going well
on your side?
You came a little later this month.
I'm just worried about you.
When you escaped from the nation of Dai,
you were ambushed.
I brought you here
and you can take charge now.
If you hadn't risked your life to save me,
I'd be dead by now.
Other than handling
the base's affairs this time,
I have something for you to do.
Please tell me.
We have a traitor at the base.
I need you to deal with it.
Who is it?
He's also from Dai.
CHU LAN
I still have your brother.
Do you not care about his life anymore?
I'm not sure
what you mean.
You've worked for me for years.
I'll give you one last chance.
Are you going to take my side
or Duke Su's?
I'll always serve you, of course.
- Where are they?
- Above us.
- How many are there?
- Three.
Are you sure?
They didn't bring
their men from the capital.
They don't get along
with local authorities
and have no reinforcements.
What language is that?
Dai Language.
Do you understand what they're saying?
Have some tea.
Where did they go?
Duke Su, since you're here,
why don't you come in and sit down?
It has been a while,
Xiao Heng.
It's him.
Since you're here,
you can forget about leaving tonight.
Let's see if you've got what it takes
to keep me here.
Watch out.
With your martial arts skills,
you're better off singing in the brothel.
You can't bear to kill her,
so I'm helping you.
Why?
Wu Lan.
Like your brother,
you're just nice to look at but useless.
My brother…
You betrayed the organization and me.
Why would I keep him alive?
Go see him in hell.
You're really heartless.
Surely Prince Cheng knows about tonight.
You don't deserve
Prince Cheng's attention.
You even drank so much before seeing me.
Well, you don't deserve
to be treated seriously.
Five against one?
As expected of Prince Cheng's subordinate.
- You're sinister enough.
- All that matters is winning.
- Are we going to die here today?
- What a jinx.
If we die together,
at least I'd have a companion.
Charge!
I knew you'd come.
Cut the nonsense.
I didn't come for you.
- You want to escape?
- In your dreams.
Get them.
Thank you, General Biao.
What general?
I've paid back my favor to Xiao Minghan.
Let's go!
When Xiao Minghan's name is cleared,
remember to invite me for drinks.
It's a deal.
My lord, he got away.
Take the rest back for interrogation.
Yes.
Governor, our informant
in the black market reported
that Lai Biao revealed the source.
As expected
of the Jiang family's daughter.
She's quite capable.
She could even make Lai Biao speak.
Let them go happily…
- and return disappointed.
- And return disappointed.
DAFENG PHARMACY
Do you still feel like vomiting?
I feel dizzy when I sit up.
Miss, I'll make you a pot of strong tea
for your hangover.
I still have a lot to do today.
I don't have time
to drink your strong tea.
Jiang Li.
Jiang Li, are you feeling better?
Let me see.
I feel much better.
Don't act tough.
You were so drunk last night.
You must feel sick today.
I had someone make you
stomach-warming red bean congee
and refreshing perilla drink.
Thank you, Jia'er.
Do you have something to ask me?
What did you
and Uncle Mingyu do yesterday?
We went to the black market in Luyang
to investigate Tuoluo flower's buyer.
If things go our way today,
the Soochow brocade case
will have a result today.
Then…
What's this?
I can't get drunk!
I'm not drunk!
What's this?
He's just…
a stranger.
A stranger?
Why did he tell me
that he's your benefactor?
He just likes to talk nonsense.
Jia'er, don't take him seriously.
Didn't you say he's a stranger?
Why did you seem
so familiar with each other?
I'll get ready and investigate
the Tuoluo flower's origin.
Wait.
Can I go with you?
Jiang Li, wherever you go,
bring me with you.
Ms. Jia'er, we have a problem.
Madam Zhuo wants to hang herself
at the government office again.
Jia'er.
You have to stay in Ye Residence
and hold the fort.
You haven't sobered up either?
How did you win yesterday?
I heard Lai Biao can drink a lot.
No one in Luyang can drink more than him.
Don't bother.
He lost in the end anyway.
Look at how smug you look.
You look just like your mother
when she was little.
Let's get down to business.
Did Lai Biao eventually tell you
who the buyer was?
The only buyer in Luyang
is Dafeng Pharmacy.
Anyone there?
DAFENG PHARMACY
- We need to get treated.
- Stop shouting.
Patients have come knocking
one after another all morning,
but no one opened the door.
They probably went out.
Where did they go?
Did they say when they'd be back?
Who knows?
They didn't even put up a notice.
They were around yesterday.
Did we alert people
when doing the challenge,
so someone leaked the news?
Let's go to Lai Biao again.
There's no hurry.
Sir, can I borrow your stool?
Take it.
- Check carefully.
- Be careful!
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
We started working
so early in the morning.
Why don't you buy me breakfast?
Eat all you want. It's on me.
Sir, two orders of steamed buns.
Right away.
Why are they here?
This is bad. Shun is still in there.
You…
Ms. Jiang Li.
What a coincidence.
You brought so many men to the pharmacy
early in the morning.
- Do you have a serious illness?
- I'm fine.
I just heard people say
that someone was killed
at Dafeng Pharmacy.
As the local official,
I rushed over before having time
to prepare my carriage.
Are you two here
because you heard the news?
We're only here for steamed buns.
Uncle Mingyu, sit.
We got tricked.
- Don't act rashly.
- Governor Tong.
The eight people in the pharmacy
were brutally murdered.
No one survived.
Eight people?
Eight lives?
Eight lives!
My goodness. Someone wiped them out.
What should we do?
We also caught a suspect.
Bring the person out!
I really came here to buy medicine.
I smelled blood from the crack in the door
and climbed over the wall to check.
Who would buy medicine from the back door?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Sit down.
Calm down.
Or not only will we fail to save Shun,
but we'll also be in trouble.
Who's your accomplice?
I was just passing by.
Ask the steamed buns seller
if you don't believe me.
I knocked for so long and only went in
because no one opened the door.
Take him back and interrogate him.
Who would do such a thing
in broad daylight in my jurisdiction?
How cruel, despicable, and insane!
I'm the one to blame.
Everyone,
I swear on my official robe
that I'll get to the bottom of this
and get justice
for Dafeng Pharmacy's eight lives!
- Justice!
I swear to fight evil
to the end!
LUYANG
Director!
Director.
Ms. Jiang Li.
The Office of Weaving and Dyeing
has concluded its investigation.
We're in a hurry to return
to the capital to report it.
What are you doing?
We haven't found out
the Tuoluo flower's origin.
Our only lead,
people in the Dafeng Pharmacy,
have been massacred.
Do you conclude cases so hastily?
Watch your words, Ms. Jiang Li.
I'm from the Office of Weaving and Dyeing.
I came to Luyang
to investigate the death
caused by Soochow brocades.
We found out the Soochow brocades
carried Tuoluo flowers,
which are highly toxic.
I have no right to investigate
where it came from.
- But the Soochow brocades--
- Ms. Jiang.
I've done my job.
What you're saying are poisoning cases.
You should turn it over
to the local government office.
Ms. Jiang Li.
Please don't make things difficult for me.
- I…
- Sir, let's go.
Is he leaving just like that?
BINGDE HALL
Could something have happened to Jiang Li?
My lady.
Jiang Li.
How did it go?
The lead is a dead end.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
You've already done a great job.
If it weren't for you,
the Ye family
might not be able to hold on until now.
Jiang Li.
You've done all you can.
We'll take it from here.
Isn't it just money?
I think I know
how much Tong Zhiyang wants.
Madam Zhuo, how is Mr. Ye doing inside?
Governor Tong, please cut to the chase.
I thought about it for a long time.
We actually have a solution
for the Soochow brocade case.
What do you mean?
Someone high up
appreciates Ye Shijie's talent
and wants to befriend the Ye family too.
It's a pity that he's so proud
that he can't tolerate
being inferior to others,
so the higher-ups
could only play some tricks
to make your nephew understand
that it's easy to break
when you're too tough.
You've gone too far.
Please don't say that.
Madam Zhuo, you also understand
that the Ye family
has been merchants for generations.
But Ye Shijie has no foundation
in the capital's bureaucracy.
He's lucky
that someone admires his talent.
It's all right
if he doesn't appreciate it.
But the Ye family should know better.
I'm just a woman.
I don't understand what you mean.
All right.
Madam Zhuo.
I won't beat around the bush.
I don't know
why you suddenly
got involved with Ms. Jiang Li
and even brought
the Office of Weaving
and Dyeing in through her.
But no matter what you do,
it'll just be all in vain.
After all, I, Tong Zhiyang
am Luyang's governor.
We just want the truth.
Madam Zhuo, you're confused.
You have the truth all along.
Open your hand
and the truth will come to you.
Clench your hand
and you'll destroy the truth.
How much do you want?
Ten thousand taels?
One hundred thousand taels?
- Gold.
- The Ye family isn't a gold mine.
We can't afford that much.
Madam Zhuo, think it over carefully.
This is today's price.
When the Ye family is desperate one day,
the price will go up.
As the saying goes,
never give up until you fail.
As long as there's a chance of survival,
the Ye family will fight for it.
Your tea is too expensive.
The Ye family can't afford it.
He's trying to bankrupt the Ye family
and cut off Shijie's retreat.
We can't let him get what he wants.
Aunt Zhuo, let me think of another way.
How can we place the Ye family's burden
on a young girl like you?
Besides, any amount of money
is just a worldly possession to us.
But now, the Ye family…
Jiang Li.
Our family has been in business
for many years.
What we see most is money.
We've seen many families
ruined by money.
It's hypocritical when others say
money means nothing to them.
In the Ye family, we dare to say that.
So what if we're wealthy?
Family matters the most.
You're our family too.
How could I let you bear the burden alone?
I hid here secretly when I was a kid
and secretly learned how the shopkeeper
bargains with customers.
Father taught me
how to do accounts step by step.
But the thought of Father being safe
is worth it.
LIZHENG HALL
I'll work hard to get it back.
Let's go home.
SHOP FOR SALE, INTERESTED BUYERS
MAY GO INSIDE FOR DETAILS
The fruits in this manor are the sweetest.
Knowing my craving,
my mother gave it to me as my dowry.
Madam Zhuo, this is all your dowry.
Why are you taking all of them out?
As long as Shijie and Mingxuan are safe,
I can bear to give up anything.
Ms. Li, get the broker.
Yes.
DATONG ESCORT AGENCY
- Miss, check out this fan.
- This may look run-down,
but this door is made of fine mahogany.
This brick was made from an official kiln.
The owner needs money.
Look. These are good wood.
I think it's just so-so.
- It's a bit old indeed.
- Uncle Mingyu.
- Come here, look.
- It's old.
- Are you selling the escort agency?
- Isn't this nice?
I don't have any business.
What's the use of keeping it?
Are you trying to raise money
for the family?
Aunt Zhuo is right.
To the Ye family,
family is far more important
than anything else.
The Ye family is in trouble now
and everyone is doing what they can.
Even someone junior in seniority like you
from the capital is working hard.
How can I stand by and watch?
I suddenly remembered
how good it was when we siblings
founded Lizheng Hall together.
But my eldest brother
and his wife suddenly died
and I ventured out on my own.
I was young and reckless then.
Who's willing to admit defeat?
I couldn't swallow my pride in the end.
Uncle Mingyu.
It's not too late yet to go home.
It's more than ten years
of resentment and anger.
The gap between us is too big.
I can't go back anymore.
- You can go back.
- I can't.
You can.
This is a deposit from the broker.
There'll be more money
after the house is sold.
- Help me give it to Madam Zhuo.
- No.
- Give it to her.
- Give it yourself.
And these…
These…
are what I've saved from traveling around
over the years.
Not much is left after opening the agency.
But these rare trinkets
can fetch a good price.
After I sell them,
give them the money too.
A song drifts over the trees to the clouds
as one dances in the moonlight.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
I just came up with an idea.
Fragrant and hot freshly-steamed buns!
Please enjoy your steamed buns.
You said you'd buy me a meal.
Is this all?
You sure know how to pick a place.
Don't underestimate the steamed buns.
These are the best steamed buns in Luyang.
The wrapper is white and fluffy
with a fresh and tender filling.
Thousands of them are sold in a day.
What do you think?
Isn't it mouthwatering
with a delicious aroma?
It's all right.
Go ahead. What's the matter?
Thank you…
for that night.
Does that mean
you remember what happened
that night?
I only remember
giving back this red cape to you.
I lent you a red cape,
so you're buying me steamed buns?
I'm also inviting you to watch a show.
I won't watch shows.
Come back.
PASTRIES
Xiao Heng.
Someone was so mad at me
for watching a show at a teahouse
that she wanted me to drink to death.
Tell me.
What show?
You've eaten the steamed bun.
Shall we start the show?
Mrs. Ye, what's the meaning of this?
I'll be straightforward.
I admit that the Ye family lost this time.
This is all that the Ye family can afford.
Please be magnanimous
and spare us.
But Mrs. Ye,
I remember warning you
to seal the deal as soon as possible.
This price
can't keep the Ye family safe.
This is the key to the Ye family's vault.
The Ye family's heirlooms,
the last things for us to survive,
are in it.
I beg you
to do justice to the Ye family.
My lord.
The house where the assassins train
was seized.
But those assassins
don't know where Chu Lan is.
- Should we use some methods?
- There's no need.
These people
don't know Chu Lan's whereabouts.
What should we do then?
Wu Lan is dead and Chu Lan is on the run.
All the leads went cold again.
Is the seized house rented or purchased?
It's rented.
Actually, they change venues every year.
It's not fixed.
Ask the landlord
who paid him the rent.
Yes.
My lord.
What's this?
Ms. Jiang Li's maid
sent over some steamed buns.
She said Ms. Jiang bought them for you.
Where's the Surveillance Commissioner?
- Urge him for Ms. Jiang Li.
- Yes.
My lord, do you think
the governor will fall for it?
If we can't succeed in one go,
won't we be laughed at in the future?
That governor is greedy and lecherous.
He's also obsessed with opera
and often indulges in it
with his subordinates.
Ms. Jiang Li is going to hit him
where it hurts.
Wait and see.
It's tasty.
One-tenth of the Ye family's fortune
will then
be yours.
The Surveillance Commissioner
received a tip
that the Ye family tributes
to the imperial court are withheld.
Is that true?
I'm Ye Mingyu.
The tributes given by the Ye family
were not withheld
but snatched away by Luyang's governor,
Tong Zhiyang.
He also imprisoned my staff, Shun,
who guarded the tributes.
Slandering a governor is a serious crime.
Is that true?
- I swear on my life.
- Lead the way.
The Ye family has a batch of tributes
for His Majesty,
but Luyang's governor,
Tong Zhiyang, took them.
I heard the imperial court
has Surveillance Commissioners
patrolling near Luyang lately.
Please pass this message
to the Surveillance Commissioner.
The Surveillance Commissioner
has his duties.
It's not worth coming to Luyang
because of a tip.
Your plan won't work.
My plan won't achieve great results
if I work on it myself.
But if you help me,
it will turn out differently.
LUYANG GOVERNMENT OFFICE
Look.
These are the Ye family's tributes.
Where's the governor?
What move is this?
- Offering presents from others?
- No.
It's called returning the items intact.
These are tributes for His Majesty
that Tong Zhiyang stole.
By the small window
I convey my grief
I received a tip
and came to investigate
Luyang governor's tribute embezzlement.
Governor Tong,
please answer in your official robe.
Tong Zhiyang is a governor after all.
He can just explain it
to the Commissioner,
return the things,
and say it's a misunderstanding.
It's not that difficult to resolve.
It's not difficult to explain it,
but the head of the Ye family
must be the one to say
that he asked
the governor and government office
to protect the tributes
instead of Tong Zhiyang
taking them for himself.
So if Tong Zhiyang wants to live,
he'll have to beg the Ye family instead.
Everything will be easy then.
You stop while you're ahead.
You draw the line just right.
I learned it from you.
But once Tong Zhiyang's case
is confirmed to be a misunderstanding,
who do you think
will be blamed for letting
the Surveillance Commissioner
come here for nothing?
If you want to eat this memorable
and juicy steamed buns
in the future,
I'll buy all of them for you.
You didn't see Tong Zhiyang's face.
He was livid.
I'm telling you, Jiang Li.
I've never felt so good.
Yes, wealth is good.
But he didn't realize wealth can kill too.
Don't they want money?
Let's give it to them.
Now that they've taken the fatal tributes,
they're going to get themselves killed.
So the Ye family does business
by not taking money we don't deserve.
I'll have to trouble you
to deal with them next.
If Tong Zhiyang wants to clear his name
with the Surveillance Commissioner,
he must help the Ye family
clarify that we were set up
for the Soochow brocades,
then release Shun.
But if we spare them,
won't they cause trouble in the future?
He won't stand a chance.
If he has different ideas,
at least Li Zhongnan won't let him
continue being Luyang's governor.
Wonderful.
Won't we be
killing two birds with one stone?
Uncle Mingyu.
You even sold
your escort agency
for the Ye family this time.
Why don't you take the chance to go home?
I'm on my uppers right now.
Why go back to let them laugh at me?
Take a guess
at what Uncle Mingxuan said
after I told him about your help
with my investigation.
He must have said I couldn't carry on
with the escort agency,
so I lost every penny.
Uncle Mingxuan didn't say that.
Uncle Mingxuan said,
"Jiang Li, your third uncle
may usually be unreliable,
but he knows
what's right and what's wrong."
He asked me to cooperate with you
and even secretly asked me
to give you the money he hid in his pillow
if the Ye family can't get through this.
He also wants me to tell you this.
He said the Ye family is broke
and asked you to get lost
and never come back.
Did he really say that?
When brothers are together,
there's peace, happiness, and harmony.
When brothers gather together,
there's profound peace and joy.
Go home.
If he really misses me that much,
I'll reluctantly do them a favor
and go home to take a peek at them.
HELP OTHERS AND MAKE YOU
AND YOUR FAMILY HAPPY
Go and switch this
to Mingxuan's favorite incense.
Yes.
- Wipe the table more.
- Yes.
The plants will be here soon.
The Four Treasures of Study.
Clean them.
Ms. Li, they're not aligned.
No. A little lower.
Yes, Madam Zhuo.
She keeps repeating
the same thing over and over.
Our home hasn't been this lively
in a long time.
You. Straighten this up.
Uncle Mingxuan is coming back today.
Uncle Mingyu is home too.
The Ye family will only be livelier
from now on.
How nice.
I used to think
our days would just be ordinary.
Only after this incident did I realize--
Jia'er.
Where's the brazier?
Make a big fire.
Great. I have to burn a fire now.
Got it. The fire girl is coming.
Good girl.
Mingyu, hang the lanterns.
Well…
Isn't Jiang Li
not doing anything here too?
Why don't you order her around?
Jiang Li is different.
She's the Ye family's savior.
How can I bear to order her around?
Go now.
Stop grumbling.
I'll do it.
Madam Zhuo, Mr. Ye is back.
- Dear!
- Mingxuan!
I'm back.
Stop. Start over.
Where's the brazier? Bring it over.
Put it here. Here.
Let your father cross over it
and get rid of bad luck.
Why didn't you
bring it to me sooner?
I have to build up my emotions again.
So it's my fault?
What are you doing? Hurry back.
Come on.
Dear!
Mingxuan!
Dear.
I missed you so much.
- I missed you more.
- I missed you even more.
I missed you even more than that.
That's enough.
There are two more people here.
Mingyu, you've done a great job this time.
Mingxuan, don't be so polite.
Mingyu, you didn't grow much
after being out for so long.
You're old now. Just beg for mercy
if you can't stand it.
You're overestimating yourself.
- Uncle Mingyu.
- Mingxuan.
- Jiang Li.
- Uncle Mingxuan.
You helped the Ye family a lot this time.
I was even suspicious of you before.
Now, it seems like
I've been petty.
Please accept my apology.
Uncle Mingxuan, please don't.
If my mother were still around,
when the Ye family was in trouble,
she wouldn't stand by and watch either.
But even though we settled
the problem this time,
the Ye family also
lost a lot of money and jewelry.
His Majesty valued Shijie and gave him
an official position in the capital.
The jewelry can be considered
a tribute from the Ye family.
Don't worry about it.
I was young
and was tricked by people.
I broke Grandmother and my uncles' hearts.
I'm still ashamed even now.
Uncle Mingxuan, Aunt Zhuo,
I'm so grateful
that you're willing to give me a chance
to make it up to you.
We can't blame you
for what happened before.
You were so young.
As elders,
we should've understood your situation.
Now that I think about it,
we made you navigate the complexities
of the Jiang family at such a young age.
Especially Ji Shuran. I…
I didn't mean to bring up what upsets you.
In the time I've spent
with Jiang Li these days,
I only think she's gentle and lovely.
She won't commit matricide and fratricide.
Ji Shuran must have set her up.
Jia'er.
It's all right, Aunt Zhuo.
Who was right and who was wrong
is already in the past.
What matters most is the present.
The top priority
is for Jiang Li to meet Mother.
Yes, Jiang Li should meet Grandmother.
Now?
Can Grandmother take it?
I can't take it that you're only
telling me about this now.
- Grandmother.
- Mother.
Grandmother, what are you doing here?
Good girl.
Let me look at you.
Grandmother.
I'm so happy that you can visit me
while I'm still alive.
Grandmother, don't you blame me
for what I did before?
You're the Ye family's
granddaughter, Jiang Li.
Jiang Li, don't worry.
The Ye family forgives you.
It's not that no one loves Ms. Jiang Li.
Other than your mother, Ye Zhenzhen,
you have so many loved ones
who care about you.
You're not alone.
And you.
Have you messed around enough outside?
Since you're back,
help your brother out,
just like this time.
Brothers can overcome any difficulties
when you work together.
Mother.
Son, come back if you're tired.
I'm always at home waiting for you.
Mother, this…
This is Mingxuan's fault.
He refused to lend me money.
If he had lent me money,
I would've come back
after settling my affairs.
Mingyu, don't think I'm scared to beat you
since Mother is here.
I think you need a beating.
You haven't come back for years.
Have you had too much fun out there?
Stand still.
- You. Stand there.
- You can't get me.
- How dare you run?
- Mother, save me.
- Stop.
- Mingxuan.
- How dare you run?
- Mother, don't protect him.
- Mother.
If Father and Xue Zhao were still around,
they'd probably also forgive me
for trusting the wrong person,
wouldn't they?
It's a pity that the people
who can forgive me
are gone.
Jiang Li, stop crying. You're home.
I'm home.